Guide to the Fales Family Papers MSS.029
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretion 2000
  - Fales, Haliburton, 1849-1929, correspondence to his mother. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1846. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1847. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1848. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1850. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1851. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1853. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1854. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1855. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband), 1858. (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Haliburton Fales (her fiance and husband),[undated]. (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from her brothers and sister-in-law (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Eliza Fales Bridgham (her sister-in-law), 1847-49., 1847-1849 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Eliza Fales Bridgham (her sister-in-law), 1850. (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Eliza Fales Bridgham (her sister-in-law), 1852-54., 1852-1854 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Eliza Fales Bridgham (her sister-in-law), 1856-58. (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Eliza Fales Bridgham (her sister-in-law), 1861. (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Eliza Fales Bridgham (her sister-in-law), [undated]. (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Harriet Mills (her sister, wife of Dr. William Mills; later, wife of William Law), 1847-49., 1847-1849 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Harriet Mills (her sister), 1849-50., 1849-1850 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Harriet Mills (her sister), 1851-53., 1851-1853 (Box 29A, Folder 27)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Harriet Mills (her sister), 1855. (Box 29A, Folder 28)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Harry Smith concerning Henry Mills's death by yellow fever, 1853. (Box 29A, Folder 29)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Harriet Law (her sister, formerly Harriet Mills), 1854-56., 1854-1856 (Box 29A, Folder 30)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Harriet Law (her sister, formerly Harriet Mills), 1860, [undated]. (Box 29A, Folder 31)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from William Law, (1856). (Box 29A, Folder 32)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Susan Marie Fales (her sister-in-law), 1847, 1849. (Box 29A, Folder 33)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Augusta Dunlap (her sister-in-law), 1854, 1856, [undated]. (Box 29A, Folder 34)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Beale, 1821-1900, correspondence from Georgiana Haliburton (Box 29A, Folder 35)
  - Fales, Susan Marie 1809-1853, correspondence from Haliburton Fales, 1852. (Box 29A, Folder 36)
  - Coggeshall, Anne Fales (sister of Samuel Fales), will and inventory; correspondence with Charles and George (her brothers) and the Munro girls (her neices)., undated (Box 29A, Folder 37)
  - Bridgham, Samuel Williard, announcement of death, 1870. (Box 29A, Folder 38)
  - Law, William, undated (Box 29A, Folder 39)
  - Beale and Fales business, undated (Box 29A, Folder 40)
  - of particular interest, letters docketed by Dorothy Mildred Mitchell Fales, undated (Box 29A, Folder 41)
  - oddments, undated (Box 29A, Folder 42)
- Accretion 2001 A: Series V, DeCoursey Fales, Jr.
  Accretion 2001 A Series V was a gift from Iten Scott Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Jr.) of material pertaining to DeCoursey Fales, Jr., dating from ca. 1940 to 1957.
  - American School of Classical Studies, 1942~54, 1942-1954 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, John Arthur, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Angelo, Hazel R., n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Battise, Minnie, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Brock, Mrs. J. W. ("Aunt Mil"), 1944 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Buckley School, 1942, 1943, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Aunt Carol, 1943, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Casson, Stanley (Oxford University), n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Challinor, David, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Christou, Grigorios, 1953, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - various church correspondents (chaplain, rector), 1942~56, 1942-1956 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Cleeve, Vera, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran, James (The Fly Club), 1942, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Cox, Frances B., n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Crawford, Lindsay, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Daniel, J. F., 1948 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Davisson, Richard L., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Dow, Sterling, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Ducey, Mrs. John F., n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - DuMont, Edgar R., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Essex Fox Hounds, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Fales, Jr., DeCoursey, 1943~57, 1943-1957 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Fales, Dorothy, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Fales, Haliburton II (brother), 1942~56, 1942-1956 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Fales, Mrs. Haliburton II ("Kak," sister-in-law), 1943~56, 1943-1956 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Fales, Haliburton III (nephew), 1955~56, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Fales, Nancy (niece), n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Fales, Priscilla (niece), n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Fales, Timothy (brother), 1942~54, 1942-1954 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Fales, Sr., DeCoursey (father), 1942~56, 1942-1956 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Flint, Jr., William Willard, 1942~45, 1942-1945 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Fly Club, 1942~57, 1942-1957 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Fowler family, 1942, 1943, n. d. (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Gambrill, Ann, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Auntie Genfrie (?), 1943 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Goldman, Richard, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Green, Theodore Francis, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Grew, John C., 1953 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - ____, Gus, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Harris, Randy, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Hartman, C. S., n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Harvard University, 1941~56, 1941-1956 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Iselin, Urling and O'Donnell, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Kellogg, Hannah, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Lake, Roy (?), 1943 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Limpert, Henry S., 1941 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Lord, Louis E., 1943 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - McCall, Harry, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - McLeod, 1954, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - M. H. R., 1953, n. d. (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous / Unidentified, undated (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Mitchell, Clarence B. (grandfather), 1942~54, 1942-1954 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Mitchell, Mrs. Clarence B. (grandmother), 1942~54, 1942-1954 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - (Mother), n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - (Mother), 1941 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - (Mother), 1942 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - (Mother), 1943 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - (Mother), 1944 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - (Mother), 1945 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - (Mother), 1946 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - (Mother), 1947 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - (Mother), 1948 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - (Mother), 1950 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - (Mother), 1951 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - (Mother), 1952 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - (Mother), 1953 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - (Mother), 1954 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - (Mother), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - (Mother), 1956 (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - (Mother), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Near East Foundation, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Neisser, Anna, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - New York University, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Pitt, Louis W., 1944 (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - Pomfret School ("Herb"), n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Prince, Jr., Mrs. Frederick H. ("Aunt Virginia"/ "Aunt GeeGee"), 1942~48, 1942-1948 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - Princeton University, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Rice, Arthur H., 1954, n. d. (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - St. Paul's School, 1943~57, 1943-1957 (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - Schlesinger, Alfred C., 1943 (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - Seales, 1947, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - Shattuck, Dr. Howard F., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - Snearline family, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 83)
  - Stowell, Lonnie, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 84)
  - ____, Sylvia, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 85)
  - Tilney, Robert W., 1943 (Box 30, Folder 86)
  - Vlamos, James F., 1941 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Wagner, Colton P., 1944~56, 1944-1956 (Box 30, Folder 88)
  - Wallace, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - Winthrop, n. d., undated (Box 30, Folder 90)
  - Yang, Tsute, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 91)
  - Zabriskie, Dr. Edwin G., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 92)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - banking and financial, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - photos (misc. / unidentified), undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - photos (misc. / unidentified), undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - biographical data, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - scholarship / academia, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - scholarship / academia, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - misc. newspaper clippings, 1953, n. d. (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - misc. Invitations / social engagements, 1954, 1955, n. d. (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - passports, undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - inventory of Haliburton Fales, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - notebooks, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - notebooks, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - pocket watch, undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - correspondence in Greek (misc. / unidentified), undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - correspondence in Greek (misc. / unidentified), undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - correspondence in Greek: Christofis, 1950-57, 1950-1957 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - correspondence in Greek: Clitos, 1951-57, 1951-1957 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - correspondence in Greek: Athenasios Kochilas, 1943-45, 1943-1945 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - correspondence in Greek: Ahmet, 1952~56, 1952-1956 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - misc. Naval Reserve, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - misc. Army, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - misc. Army, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - misc. Army, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - misc. Army, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - misc. Army, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - misc. Army, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - misc. Army maps and targets, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Accretion 2001 B: Series I, Fales Family
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes nineteenth and twentieth century correspondence and photos, ephemera, mementos, and books. The accretion was not subdivided into series. Note: Box 39A contains Oversize Photos etc.
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1916/1928/1929, 1916-1929 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1948 A-Z (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1949 A-Z (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1950 A-K (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1950 L-Z (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1951 A-E (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1951 F-L (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1951 M-Z (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1952 A-K (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1952 L-Z (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1953 A-E (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1953 F-L (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1953 M-Z (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1954 A-K (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1954 L-Z (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1955 A-K (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1955 L-Z (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1956 A-E (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1956 F-L (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1956 M-Z (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1957 A-E (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1957 F-L (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1957 M-Z (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1958 A-K (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1958 L-Z (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1959 A-K (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1959 L-Z (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1960 A-E (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1960 F-L (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1960 M-Z (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1961 A-E (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1961 F-L (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1961 M-Z (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1962 A-K (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1962 L-Z (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1963 A-K (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1963 L-Z (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1964 A-K (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1964 L-Z (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1965 A-K (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1965 L-Z (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1966 A-K (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1966 L-Z (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1967 A-E (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1967 F-L (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1967 M-Z (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1968 A-K (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1968 L-Z (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1969 A-Z (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - correspondence to Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) date unidentifiable, undated (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - correspondence from Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1916-1945 & n. d. (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - correspondence from Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) 1947-1960 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - holiday cards (assorted; n. d.), undated (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Colonial Dames of America: Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.), undated (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) passport, undated (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) Europe trip 1960 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Dorothy Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Sr.) medical & health 1961-1966 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - sewing book: Dorothy Mitchell Fales & Nancy Fales, undated (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Sr.: 1916-1926 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Sr.: 1931-1948 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Sr.: 1950-1965; n. d. (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - correspondence to DeCoursey Fales Sr.: 1929-1966 A-Z; n. d. (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - wedding of DeCoursey Fales Sr. to Dorothy Mitchell: June 1917 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - DeCoursey Sr. & Dorothy Fales' 40th anniversary: June 1957 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - DeCoursey Fales Sr.: Harvard rowing 1908 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - DeCoursey Fales Sr.'s war service flag: WWI, undated (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - DeCoursey Fales Sr.: memorial booklet, undated (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1935-1948 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1949 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1950 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1951 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1952 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1953 (Box 36, Folder 73)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1954 (Box 36, Folder 74)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 75)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1957 (Box 36, Folder 76)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1958 (Box 36, Folder 77)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1959 (Box 36, Folder 78)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1960 (Box 36, Folder 79)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1961 (Box 36, Folder 80)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1962 (Box 36, Folder 81)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1963 (Box 36, Folder 82)
  - correspondence from DeCoursey Fales Jr.: 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 83)
  - DeCoursey Fales Jr.: school reports & school correspondence (Buckley, St. Paul's, Harvard), undated (Box 36, Folder 84)
  - correspondence from Iten Scott Fales (Mrs. DeCoursey Jr.) 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 85)
  - correspondence from Haliburton Fales II: 1942-1968 (Box 36, Folder 86)
  - Haliburton Fales II: school reports & school correspondence, undated (Box 36, Folder 87)
  - correspondence from Timothy Fales: 1947-1959 (Box 36, Folder 88)
  - correspondence from Timothy Fales: 1960-1963 (Box 36, Folder 89)
  - Timothy Fales: school reports, correspondence, mementos, undated (Box 36, Folder 90)
  - wedding of Timothy Fales and Ellen Wood: Dec 1953 (Box 36, Folder 91)
  - correspondence from Josephine Premice Fales (Mrs. Timothy): 1959-1968; n. d. (Box 37, Folder 92)
  - marriage of Timothy Fales and Josephine Premice: hate mail & news items, undated (Box 37, Folder 93)
  - correspondence to Haliburton Fales I: 1916, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 94)
  - Nancy Fales Martin: resume 1966 (Box 37, Folder 95)
  - joke letter (n. d.) sent by Thomas Lovell, undated (Box 37, Folder 96)
  - Bessie Young: Mitchell family nurse, undated (Box 37, Folder 97)
  - life of Daniel A. Lindley: Mitchell/Blair family forebear (?), undated (Box 37, Folder 98)
  - children's art: Lucy, Priscilla, Bill, Enrico (?), undated (Box 37, Folder 99)
  - essays by Clarence Blair Mitchell, undated (Box 37, Folder 100)
  - Far Hills Country Day School: school plays, commencement programs 1953-1967 (Box 37, Folder 101)
  - St. Timothy's School: alumnae bulletins 1948-1958 (Box 37, Folder 102)
  - St. Timothy's School: alumnae bulletins 1961-1968 (Box 37, Folder 103)
  - Buckley School: "The Dawn" (magazine) 1927-1937 (Box 37, Folder 104)
  - Buckley (?) School magazine: "The Junior Herald" (1931)/ "The Senior Cobra" (193-?) (Box 37, Folder 105)
  - St. Paul's School: "Pictorial" and "Horae Scholasticae", 1936-1937 (Box 37, Folder 106)
  - social events: 1910-1954 (Box 37, Folder 107)
  - social events: 1960-1969; n. d. (Box 37, Folder 108)
  - social & business: 1953-1968 (Box 37, Folder 109)
  - social & business: 1950-1964 (Box 37, Folder 110)
  - travel & tour guidebooks, undated (Box 37, Folder 111)
  - travel & tour guidebooks: Britain, undated (Box 37, Folder 112)
  - Essex Fox Hounds, undated (Box 37, Folder 113)
  - Tewksbury Foot Bassets, undated (Box 37, Folder 114)
  - Bernardsville Hills (magazine): Sept 1905; May 1906, 1905-1906 (Box 37, Folder 115)
  - St. Luke's Episcopal Church, undated (Box 37, Folder 116)
  - Garden Club ca. 1946-1964 (Box 37, Folder 117)
  - NYU: Fales & Gallatin programs, undated (Box 38, Folder 118)
  - civil defense guidelines: Bedminster Township, NJ (n. d.), undated (Box 38, Folder 119)
  - arts & antiques, undated (Box 38, Folder 120)
  - residences: Vernon Manor, Peapack, NJ; Marble Palace (Prince family), Newport, RI (Box 38, Folder 121)
  - paper on career of Theodore Francis Green: 1959 (Box 38, Folder 122)
  - ships: images, clippings, undated (Box 38, Folder 123)
  - gymkhana races @ Pennbrook Farm 1909-1911 (Box 38, Folder 124)
  - Bryn Mawr Hound Show: ca. 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 125)
  - receipts: furnishings, antiques, gifts, home dr, undated (Box 38, Folder 126)
  - Brady House, Nassau: Helen & Ruth Brady, undated (Box 38, Folder 127)
  - sketch of Fales family geneology, undated (Box 38, Folder 128)
  - Family Record 1800's (Box 38, Folder 129)
  - diary of "Fraulein" (Mrs. Antonie Ziegler, Fales family nurse): 1892 (Box 38, Folder 130)
  - excerpt from John Mitchell journal: 1825 (Box 38, Folder 131)
  - Clarence Van Schaik Mitchell: award (n. d.), undated (Box 38, Folder 132)
  - letter from "Kate" to "Brother": 1842 (Box 38, Folder 133)
  - city taxes: 1850's-1860's, 1850-1860 (Box 38, Folder 134)
  - city taxes: 1870's-1880's, 1870-1880 (Box 38, Folder 135)
  - city taxes: 1890's (Box 38, Folder 136)
  - social: ca. 1919 (Box 38, Folder 137)
  - correspondence to Samuel Bradford Fales: 1830's; n. d. (Box 38, Folder 138)
  - Samuel Fales Dunlap: correspondence, receipts, accounts ca. 1830-1890 (Box 38, Folder 139)
  - correspondence to "Lizzie": ca. 1840's-1850's, 1840-1850 (Box 38, Folder 140)
  - correspondence to Susan Maria Fales (b. 1809) (Box 38, Folder 141)
  - correspondence to Elizabeth (Eliza?) Fales (b. 1813) (Box 38, Folder 142)
  - correspondence from Haliburton Fales (b. 1815) (Box 38, Folder 143)
  - estate of Samuel Fales Dunlap: as rec'd ca. 1846, upon turning 21 (Box 38, Folder 144)
  - will of Andrew Dunlap: 1835 (Box 38, Folder 145)
  - correspondence to Augusta (Mrs. Andrew) Dunlap: ca. 1830's - 1840's, 1830-1840 (Box 38, Folder 146)
  - will of Samuel Fales (n. d.), undated (Box 38, Folder 147)
  - correspondence from Samuel Fales Dunlap (in Europe) to family: 1846-1847 (Box 38, Folder 148)
  - estate of James Dunlap: executor's account; inventory; ca. 1801-1805 (Box 38, Folder 149)